Okay, with that, I think the final thing we want to end on
is deploying your app.
So we're going to take a couple minutes to take a look at that.
So when it comes to deploying your app,
if you do it the standard way,
you usually have to do like an FTP server,
and you got to build this thing, right?
Because after all, if we take a look at our Say Love View app,
this is not something that we can just drop on a server and it would just work.
We need to actually build the thing.
So the way this works,
if you take a look at your package.json inside of Say Love View,
you'll see that there's actually a build command that we can run.
So let's go ahead and do that, shall we?
So inside of here, we're going to Say Love View and NPM Run Build.
And right now, there's a bunch of stuff in there,
so let me clean that up real quick.
Okay, NPM Run Build. There we go.
Okay. And what that will build for you is a disk folder,
which stands for basically to distributed folder.
And inside of here, now this should look like something you can actually deploy
where you have your index.html.
You can see that there's generated hashes for your different assets,
for CSS, JavaScript, managing those things.
And you might notice that look,
those chunks that we did when we did the routes, here they are.
They're already parsed out for us because the bundler already did that for us.
Now, of course, deploying this can be done a number of ways,
but I'll just be showing you how to do this in sort of a
Git-based format rather than just dropping it on the server.
And so all this will take, so this is, I guess,
shout out for the company I work for, Netlify.
So if you have a free account, this will work fairly easily.
So what I'm going to do here,
I'm going to go ahead and log in to my account.
And what we're going to do is just we're going to create a new site.
And so the reason this is really nice is because what you're doing here
is you're creating a pipeline that connects your GitHub repo
that you're basically committing all your code to, to your deployments.
So basically, it's similar to the way you want it to watch for
reactive things and view to do things.
This will watch your repo and when you make changes to it,
it will then run new deployments.
And so here, if we go complete intro, that should show up,
do, do, once we give it a little bit.
There we go, complete intro to view three.
And then we have a branch to deploy.
And so since my currently, my CELA view really does need to be 16,
so I'm going to be deploying the 16 solution branch,
but normally you'll be deploying your main branch.
And then the base directory is, for me,
it's going to be CELA view because we have multiple apps running
inside of the project right now.
So that's the specific one I want to build.
And then we're going to run the command npm run build.
And the directory though, we have to remember,
is what's actually being outputted.
It's a disk directory.
And so that's what's being configured.
And so once we run that, we get something that's pretty great.
So for anyone who used to do things in the old days
where you did FTP servers,
you had to manage a lot of caching, right?
If you uploaded a CSS file, you had to manage like,
oh, is the user going to get the right thing?
Like, are they looking at the same version?
And so oftentimes when you're debugging things,
it's hard to figure out what's going on
because what your user's seeing might not be what you're seeing.
And so in the effort of having Git deployments, basically,
one of the things that Netlify does for you,
and there are other companies that do this as well,
so this is not the only one,
is that you'll see here that automatically generated for me
a random URL that I could share with people.
And so you can see here that all my functionality
is in here, actually.
So if I can continue with emails, it's live,
which is great.
That happened in a matter of seconds.
And then the other thing too is that with the domain settings,
it's pretty easy for us to then say,
let's go ahead and swap this out,
and I'm going to call this say love you.
Granted, this is where it gets to it first.
But now that I've swapped it out,
we can see now that when I open it up, there we go.
Say love you.netlify.app, and it just works.
And the beautiful part about this
is not so much that it deploys,
because again, there are many ways to deploy.
It's the fact that it'll watch your GitHub repository.
So in other words, if you go inside
of the app.view right now for say love you,
and then instead at the very top, we'll say something,
let's see, from here, we'll say this is a new message.
And then I think I did a triple S on that,
let me fix that.
And then if we commit this to our branch,
so say love you here, and then ignore this stuff for now.
One, two, three, four, five.
Git commit feature, add new message.
And then I push on this branch.
One of the things you'll see is that in the deploy,
it'll actually, basically there's a hook
to watch GitHub repo, and it knows,
hey, it's time to make another build.
And so you can see here, it's going off, it's running,
it's building the thing, that's fine.
And so what's really cool about this though,
is that when it's running this build,
it's basically doing an atomic deploy.
So what that means is that it's completely separate
from the previous deploy, because that was a problem
with a lot of enterprise systems,
is that once you push a deploy,
you weren't sure what the assets were,
and so especially if you're having users with issues,
it was hard to debug, and then let alone rollbacks,
it was kind of a nightmare to deal with all of that.
It's okay, our site is live, so we can see now,
if I go over to my, over here, you see,
hey look, this is a new message, it's right here.
But again, in the effort of the atomic deploy model,
what if your product manager is like,
whoa, whoa, whoa, we don't want this message,
that is a bug?
Well, typically what you'd have to do is,
you have to get your engineers, you have to be like,
hurry up, we gotta figure out what's going on,
and you gotta push the right code, right?
But no, what you can do, because of the atomic deploy,
is we can come in here, and if we can actually just say,
you know what, we're gonna go ahead,
and do, do, do, do, inside of here,
we can publish this deploy instead, whoop, not this one,
there you go, click publish deploy, and we publish it,
and what you'll see now is that it's switched now,
from the latest commit, and what we have here,
when we go back to our URL, voila,
users, everything's fixed.
And so this is a kind of a, this is basically,
I would say, the modern way when it comes to
thinking of deployment, in that,
especially because we use a lot of Git versioning,
why shouldn't our deploys also be versioned in a way
that allows us to go ahead, and whether it's split testing,
or ensure that we deliver the same things to our users,
this is just something that I wanted to show you all,
and how you can deploy your app with view.